(Leonard:)Yeah, I know who it
is, but why is it me?
(Raj:)You're right. It should
be a cuddly Asian boy.
(Howard:)Like me.
"And Absolon hath
kist hir nether ye,
"and Nicholas is scalded
in the towte.
(Amy:)This tale is doon,
and God save al the rowte."
(Penny:)What the hell was that?
(Amy:)Bernadette dared me to
tell a dirty story.
"The Miller's Tale" by Chaucer
is the dirtiest story I know.
(Amy:)It would have been hidden
in sock drawers
(Amy:)if people in the 14th century
had worn socks.
(Bernadette:)I thought it was pretty spicy.
(Bernadette:)Especially the part
where he kisses her nether ye.
(Amy:)You might not
like it as much
(Amy:)if you knew what
"nether ye" meant.
(Amy:)if one cares
about hygiene,
(Amy:)one ought not be kissing it.
(Bernadette:)Okay, my turn.
(Bernadette:)Penny, truth or dare?
(Amy:)Truth.
(Bernadette:)Why are you still hanging out
with Leonard so much
(Bernadette:)even though you broke up
with him?
(Amy:)Oh, that's an
excellent question.